somatix.ai 2018-01-23

# Takt | Privacy Policy

**Effective Date:** July 5th, 2016

Takt, Inc. (“Takt”) values your privacy. In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe how we collect, use and disclose information that we obtain about visitors to our website [www.takt.com](http://www.takt.com/) (the “Site”) and users of the services available through our Site (collectively, the “Services”). 

By visiting the Site or using any of our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of our Site or Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Use, available at <http://www.takt.com/terms> and incorporated by reference into this Policy (including applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes). 

###  What Information Do We Collect About You and Why? 

We may collect information about you directly from you and from third parties, as well as automatically through your use of our Site or Services. 

Information We Collect Directly From You. You may browse the Site without registering. However, if you would like to sign up for emails from us or if you request other information from us, we may collect your name, email, phone number and other contact information, as well as your company name and other information. In addition, if you are interested in a job with us, we may collect your name and contact information, resume, job history or other relevant information through the Site. In addition, we may assign authorized users a username and password to access the Takt portal. 

Information We Collect Automatically. We may automatically collect the following information about your use of our Site or Services through cookies, web beacons, java script, log files and other technologies: your domain name; your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; the length of time you visit our Site and or use our Services; and the referring URL, or the webpage that led you to our Site; access time; device ID. We may combine this information with other information that we have collected about you, including, where applicable, your name and other personal information Please see the section “Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms” below for more information. 

###  How We Use Your Information 

We use your information, including your personal information, for the following purposes: 

  * To provide our Services to you, to communicate with you about your use of our Services, to respond to your inquiries, to fulfill your orders, and for other customer service purposes.
  * To consider you for positions with Takt for which you have expressed interest or may be interested in, and to contact you about potential positions.
  * To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, to offer location customization, and personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the Site or our Services.
  * For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we may use your information, such as your email address, to send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about products or information we think may interest you. We also may use the information that we learn about you to assist us in advertising our Services on third party websites.
  * To better understand how users access and use our Site and Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, in order to improve our Site and Services and respond to user desires and preferences, and for other research and analytical purposes.

###  How We Share Your Information 

We may share your information, including personal information, as follows: 

  * Affiliates. We may disclose the information we collect from you to our affiliates or subsidiaries; however, if we do so, their use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information will be consistent with this Policy. 
  * Service Providers. We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf. 
  * Business Transfers. If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other company. 
  * In Response to Legal Process. We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, a subpoena, or other legal process. 
  * To Protect Us and Others. We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which Takt is involved. 
  * Aggregate and De-Identified Information. We may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or similar purposes. 

###  Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms 

We use cookies, clear GIFs, log files and other tracking mechanisms to collect information about your use of our Sites and Apps, as described above. We may combine this information with other personal information we collect from you. Currently, our systems do not recognize browser “do-not-track” requests. You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in this section (e.g., by disabling cookies). 

**Cookies**   
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies enable a faster log-in process, and some allow us to track your activities at our Sites. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to disable cookies or change your cookies settings. 

**Clear GIFs, pixel tags and other technologies**   
Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, which are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags), in connection with our Sites to track the activities of visitors to our Sites, help us manage content, and compile statistics about usage of our Sites. We may also use clear GIFs in HTML emails to our clients, to help us track email response rates, identify when our emails are viewed, and track whether our emails are forwarded. 

**Third-Party Analytics**   
We also use automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate usage of our Sites and the services we provide. We use these tools to gather non-personal information about users to help us improve our services, performance and user experiences. These analytics providers may use cookies and other technologies to perform their services, and may combine the information that they collect about you on our Sites with other information that they have collected. This Policy does not cover such third parties’ use of the data. 

### Plug-ins and Social Media Widgets 

Our Site may include social media features and widgets, such as the Facebook Like button and the "Share this" button, as well as other interactive mini-programs that run on our Site and Services and enable certain features to work (e.g., blogs and comments). These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly and for purposes. These features are displayed on our Site, but are hosted by third parties, and are subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them 

###  Third-Party Ad Networks 

We use third parties such as network advertisers to display advertisements to assist us in displaying advertisements on third party websites, and to evaluate the success of our advertising campaigns. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Site as well as other websites. This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements by displaying ads for products and services in which you might be interested. Third party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Site and our services, as well as aggregate or non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our Site and users of our service. 

You may opt-out of many third-party ad networks, including those operated by members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). For more information regarding this practice by NAI members and DAA members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to opt-out of third-party ad networks operated by NAI and DAA members, please visit their respective websites: [www.networkadvertising.org/opt...](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) (NAI) and [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) (DAA). 

Opting out of one or more NAI member or DAA member networks (many of which will be the same) only means that those members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you. It does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content or ads. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI or DAA opt-out may no longer be effective. Additional information is available on NAI’s and DAA’s websites accessible by the above links. 

###  Third-Party Links 

Our Site and Services may contain links to third-party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites. 

###  Security of My Personal Information 

We have implemented security measures to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security. 

###  What Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information? 

We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you. You may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the e-mail. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us. 

###  Children Under 13 

Our Services are not designed for children under 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our systems. 

###  Contact Us 

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Services or would like to make a complaint, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3b484e4b4b54494f7b4f5a504f15585456). 

###  Changes to this Policy 

This Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Policy on our Site, at <http://www.takt.com/privacy-policy>. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site, or notifying users via email.
